## **SUMMARY**

Educated as a Mechanical Engineer focused in Control Systems. 7 years of experience shipping industry leading software in both a QA Engineer and Interaction Design capacity. Currently building web application user interfaces with HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript/jQuery.

#### SKILLS

Proven ability to ship high quality, well-designed web and desktop products. Excellent collaboration, written and verbal communication, and leadership skills.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# **Front End Engineer**

Shocase

2013 - Present

Building Front End experiences for a brand new social network.

## Web Design Engineer

Autodesk, Inc.

2012 - 2013

Implementing dynamic, scalable, robust, responsive and cross-browser user experiences in HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript / jQuery for the Autodesk Knowledge Network.

# Web Design Engineer (Rotation)

Autodesk, Inc.

11/2011 - 1/2012

Developing a semantic, cross-browser user experience in HTML/CSS for the "Locate a Reseller" page on Autodesk.com.

## **Principal Interaction Designer**

Autodesk, Inc.

2007-2012

Working with product managers, engineers, and user researchers to design and document features for the industry leading AutoCAD 2009-2013 (Windows) and AutoCAD 2011-2013 (Mac) products.

#### Test Development Engineer/Lead

Autodesk, Inc.

2004-2007

Responsible for the quality of multiple features over the course of three yearly AutoCAD releases (2006/2007/2008). Worked closely with other functional groups to help develop usable, high-quality, well documented AutoCAD features.

## **EDUCATION**

#### University of California, Los Angeles

M.S. Mechanical Engineering (2003-2004)

# **University of California, Berkeley**

B.S. Mechanical Engineering (1998-2003)

## PROFICIENCIES & INTERESTS

Code HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, PHP, Git, SVN

**Tools** Adobe Creative Suite, OmniGraffle, AutoCAD

Personal Teaching/Playing Percussion, Beer Brewing, Mountain/Road Biking

# Shekhar Khedekar

# CONTACT

shekhar.khedekar@gmail.com 510.220.9106 linkedin.com/in/shekharkhede

linkedin.com/in/shekharkhedekar facebook.com/shekhar.khedekar